

PHÙNG HOÀNG PHÚ LỘC

WEB DEVELOPER

Male



0912698173



Nov 5, 1999

phunghoangphuloc@gmail.com

HoaVang - DaNang - VietNam

66

Currently, I graduated from Duy Tan University with an average score of 3.2. During my four years at school, I have learned many programming languages as well as soft skills. Especially, I'm a fluent web language programmer. So I find myself perfectly matching the company job description. I hope my knowledge can contribute to the development of your company

Education

Duy Tan University, Graduation Certificate

2017 - 2021

Major: Software Engineer

GPA: 3.2/4 Level: Excellent

NPH High School, Violympic Online - Math

2010 - 2011

Prize: the third prize

NPH High School, Young computer Scientist

2010 - 2011

Prize: the third prize

HT1 Primary School, Provincial Merit Competition

2009 - 2010

Prize: the third prize

Work experience

BitiLand Company, Web Developer

MAR 2021 - PRESENT

Main duties performed:

- Wordpress

Duy Tan University, Capstone ViboTour

AUG 2020 - APR 2021

Main duties performed:

- Collecting Request - Creating Document

Skills

Programming Language:

Pascal, C++, Java, PHP, JS, Wordpress

Database:

SQL Server, Postgresql, Mysql

Language:

English (good communication)

Soft Skill:

Self-study, Teamwork, Work under pressure

Interests

- Hanging out with a close friend
- Having dinner with all family member
- Playing sport
- Play video game
- Working with my pc

- Developing Product
- Testing

Acexis JSC, Internship

APR 2018 - FEB 2019

Main duties performed:

- Being trained on JS language
- Experience the working environment in the business
- Learning company workflow

CGV Cinema, Part Time Job

APR 2018 - FEB 2019

Main duties performed:

- Selling
- Clearing
- Training the newbie